

# Mario González Duarte

FRONT END DEVELOPER

### **Profile**

15+ years of experience in front end development with a wide range of technical skills and a deep understanding of the latest technologies and trends. Committed, dedicated, proactive and ability to be decisive. Team player, with predisposition for helping and/or transmitting knowledge, providing mentoring and support. In addition to development, I'm also interested in technical lead and front end architect roles.

## **Work Experience**

### Front end developer, SEDDI

Madrid (Spain)

June 2023 - Present

Working in different company ReactJS projects as Textura web application.

• Improve the design, functionalities and performance of the main product of the company: Textura. Always improving it and giving value to our customers.

#### **Freelance**

Madrid (Spain)

July 2022 - June 2023

Working on various projects related to web3 and blockchain technology.

- Design and development of a marketplace for Stream Dungeons NFT game, in Angular and SASS (https://nft.streamdungeons.com)
- Collaboration in play-to-earn game projects, smart contracts interaction and Metamask with React.
- Update my expertise and skills in Angular and React with training courses. Web3 and smart contracts interaction training.

# Front end developer and Architect, Copado Holdings Inc

Madrid (Spain)

May 2019 - July 2022

- Worked on some of the best known applications of the company such as Data Templates and Pipeline.
- Creating Value Stream Maps app from scratch, achieving to record a patent.
- Designed and developed generic Lightning Web Components to be reused by other developers in other parts of the application.
- Worked closely with the design department to convert the new company look and feel design in real CSS layouts.
- Refactoring and technical support to workmates.

#### Front end Architect, VASS

Madrid (Spain)

November 2017 - May 2019

Hired as a front end architect to collaborate in the design and development of different company projects Angular applications, several onboardings apps and various POC projects.

- Designed and developed an Angular library made up of components to be used by developers in their projects.
- Implemented a front end architecture in Ferrovial.
- Technical support to workmates and technical interviews to new candidates.

#### **Details**

Madrid, Spain

**L** +34 679 84 97 84

September 26th 1982

### **Skills**

React

Angular

Javascript

Typescript

Lightning Web Components

AngularJS

jQuery

Webpack

HTML<sub>5</sub>

CSS / SASS / LESS

Responsive Design

**API REST** 

Git

Node JS

Jest

TDD

Agile Methodologies

Adobe Photoshop

# Languages





Spanish

Fnalish

### Javascript front end developer, Efron Consulting Inc

Boston, MA. USA April 2015 - November 2017

• Worked at Isban developing different internal Santander USA bank applications.

• Designed and built a development environment which provided an architecture and a controlled environment to programming, in order to give crossover components and widgets to be used by developers in their projects.

### Javascript front end developer, Adesis Netlife SL

Madrid, Spain October 2011 - April 2015

• Javascript developer in important customers such as BBVA Bancomer Mexico, Repsol, Bankia and Mapfre.

• At Mapfre, I worked in the establishment of a new and better front end architecture, developing new crossover component, initial developments (Zero versions) and experimental projects.

• Lead and mentor a 5 developers team at Bankia.

### Front end developer, Atmira Espacio de consultoría

Madrid, Spain November 2008 - October 2011

I worked in Web applications for several Saving Banks at Confederación Española de Cajas de Ahorros (CECA).

### Internship assistant, Cantabria Government Admin.

Santander, Spain August 2006 - October 2008

Internship assistant at Cantabria Education Office (Spain), doing admin tasks as webmaster in the government educative site (Educantabria)

### **Education**

High Degree Professional Training (CFGS) in Management Information Systems. Computer and Information Sciences.

IES Alisal. Santander, Spain

# Other interesting data

Drive license B

Hobbies: photography, films and TV shows, music, traveling,

dancing, technology, reading

**Linkedin:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/mario-gonzalez-duarte

**Github:** https://github.com/magodu **More info:** www.mariogonzalezduarte.es

### Soft skills

Fast learner Team player

Mentoring Support

Problem solving

#### Courses

React Angular

Typescript LWC

Clean Code AngularJS

NodeJS Memory Leaks

Closures Polymer

.NET Web design

Photoshop E-commerce

Java